With population increases and global urbanisation ever accelerating, much attention is focused on the sustainability of our cities and scant attention is paid to the countryside.
随着人口增长和全球城市化不断加速，人们把大量注意力集中在城市的可持续性上，对乡村却关注甚少。
Rural life is associated with closely knit communities, a sense of belonging, and a simple, tranquil life.
乡村生活让人联想到关系紧密的社区、归属感以及简单宁静的生活。
Yet whilst some or all of these elements exist in the countryside, so do conservatism and a lack of employment opportunities.
然而，乡村虽然存在上述部分或全部要素，但同样存在保守思想和就业机会匮乏的问题。
And it is mostly due to the latter that rural communities are suffering.
而乡村社区之所以陷入困境，主要就是因为后者。
Attracted by the improved economics of urban areas, country-dwellers across the world are moving out, contributing to the excessive crowdedness of densely populated cities, and leaving the countryside in desolation.
受城市地区经济状况改善的吸引，世界各地的乡村居民正纷纷迁出，加剧了人口稠密城市的过度拥挤，也让乡村陷入一片荒凉。
So how can the countryside ensure its survival among these changes—or should it at all?
那么，在这些变化之中，乡村怎样才能确保自身的存续？又或者，乡村究竟该不该存续下去？
Due to both the distance between residences and facilities and often intermittent public transport, those living in the countryside are heavier automobile users.
由于住所与各种设施相距较远，加之公共交通往往班次稀少，住在乡村的人用车更多。
Rural dwellers also use more energy maintaining their mostly detached buildings.
乡村居民的房屋大多是独栋的，他们维护这些房屋也要耗费更多能源。
We may be piled up like boxes in the city, but this brings energy efficiency that the countryside cannot match.
在城市里，我们或许像箱子一样层层堆叠，但这带来了乡村无法比拟的能源效率。
Rural energy requirements result in higher carbon emissions per person than in the city, so it is actually irresponsible to endorse such a lifestyle choice.
乡村的能源需求导致人均碳排放量高于城市，因此，赞同人们选择这样的生活方式其实是不负责任的。
Protecting the countryside is a hot topic.
保护乡村是一个热门话题。
Those who have made their fortunes in the city often buy second homes in the countryside, visiting intermittently for a sample of a supposedly simple life.
那些在城市里发了财的人常常在乡村购置第二套住房，不时去那里体验一番所谓的简单生活。
The side-effect of this is that house prices are pushed up due to increased demand, leaving them unaffordable for local people.
这带来的副作用是，需求增加推高了房价，让当地人负担不起。
A solution has yet to be found for this challenge, for market forces are further forcing residents out of the countryside.
这一难题至今尚未找到解决办法，因为市场力量正进一步迫使居民离开乡村。
For those who believe in rural preservation, this is deplorable.
对那些主张保护乡村的人来说，这种情况令人痛惜。
Whilst an idealised view of the countryside is common, the reality is that rural life has continuously evolved.
虽然把乡村理想化的看法很常见，但现实是，乡村生活一直在不断演变。
Industrialisation brought an increase in divisions of labour, changing social links between rural people.
工业化使劳动分工更加细化，改变了乡村居民之间的社会联系。
The internet has introduced once-foreign cultures into the countryside.
互联网已把曾经陌生的文化引入乡村。
Improved travel connections and affordability have made the world more accessible, creating a “global village”.
交通线路得到改善，出行也更加实惠，这让世界各地变得更容易到达，从而造就了一个“地球村”。
Considering these changes, surely an evolving countryside is inevitable.
考虑到这些变化，乡村不断演变无疑是不可避免的。
Perhaps the countryside should also prepare itself for massive population increases in the future.
也许乡村也应该为未来人口的大幅增长做好准备。
With cities across the world growing rapidly, how will the current urban generation respond to the inevitable social changes of mass urbanisation?
随着世界各地的城市迅速扩张，当今这一代城市人将如何应对大规模城市化带来的种种不可避免的社会变化？
Will the longing for a simpler life become stronger, fueling a rural renaissance?
对更简单生活的向往会不会变得更加强烈，从而推动乡村复兴？
As the world continues to urbanise, the voices calling for rural preservation may well grow louder.
随着世界持续城市化，呼吁乡村保护的声音很可能会越来越响亮。
But change is inevitable.
但变化是不可避免的。
We know that the world is going to see new cities emerging from the dust and current cities growing into megacities, but the future of the countryside is less clear.
我们知道，世界将会见证新城市拔地而起、现有城市发展为特大城市，但乡村的未来却没那么明朗。